[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where did the TAM Airlines Flight 3054 deadly accident from July 17, 2007 occur?", "correct_answer": "Brazil", "incorrect_answers": ["Jamaica", "United States", "Tahiti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Perfect Storm, the crew has no idea they were heading into the storm, because their equipment fails, and the weather report never gets to them.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A farmer and his son are working together. The farmer is carrying one sack of grain and the son is carrying two sacks. Who was carrying the heavier load- the son or the father?", "correct_answer": "the father", "incorrect_answers": ["the son", "They werent carrying anything.", "the same amount"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many teeth do slugs have?", "correct_answer": "3,000", "incorrect_answers": ["2,000", "1,000", "None"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This percentage of all snakes on Earth are lethal to humans.", "correct_answer": "15%", "incorrect_answers": ["10%", "20%", "25%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Wayans duo created the television series In Living Color?", "correct_answer": "Keenen and Damon", "incorrect_answers": ["Damon and Dwayne", "Shawn and Marlon", "Kim and Nadia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous writer is not paired with the correct pseudonym?", "correct_answer": "Ellery Queen-Erle Stanley Gardner", "incorrect_answers": ["Ellis Bell-Emily Bronte", "Richard Bachman-Stephen King", "Ernest V. Trueblood-William Faulkner"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tiger sharks are know to eat garbage that is thrown in the water by humans.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Molecular electronic transitions (n to \u03a0* or \u03a0 to \u03a0*) are are usually caused by the input of infrared radiation.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did actor and director Mel Gibson voice in the 1995 animated movie Pocahontas?", "correct_answer": "John Smith", "incorrect_answers": ["Governor Ratcliffe", "Chief Powhatan", "Kocoum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tab Fielding is a corporate/government murderer in Soylent Green. Who plays this character?", "correct_answer": "Chuck Conners", "incorrect_answers": ["Joseph Cotton", "Charles Bronson", "Brock Peters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This oil field, located south of Beaumont, Texas, and discovered by Anthony Francis Lucas, was the first major oil field in the USA.", "correct_answer": "Spindletop Oil Field", "incorrect_answers": ["Thunder Horse Field", "Wilmington Oil Field", "Elk Hills Field"]}]